<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:iltalehti="https://www.iltalehti.fi/rss" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs</link>
    <description>None</description>
    <language>fi</language>
    <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 18:12:59 +0300</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Helsingin edustalla on saari, jossa aika on pysähtynyt vuoteen 1952: ”Emme seuraa trendejä”</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>health</category>
      <pubDate>2019-06-21</pubDate>
      <description>Aivan kuin aika olisi pysähtynyt Pyysaaressa, Helsingin
            edustalla kelluvalla Helsingin kaupungin omistamalla
            pienellä saarella Laajasalon ja Kulosaaren välissä. Tuntuu kuin saaressa olisi aina olympiavuosi 1952.
            Omaleimaista tunnelmaa saarelle luo 1900-luvun alun huvilassa toimiva ravintola Pyysaari, joka tunnetaan
            myös
            nimellä Palma de Pyy.
            Ravintola aloitti toimintansa vuonna 1952, kun
            Helsinkiin saapui kisavieraita olympialaisiin ja joukko anniskelulupia myönnettiin lisää.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The pilot episode, in 1959, aired a decade before the first moon landing, which is celebrating its 50th
            anniversary.</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://publication.blendleimg.com/publication/newyorktimes/2019/07/02/item/34_1/version/1/image/original/1bce4ea30f8b96ce4ce89710f9d4095a78fdf43b.jpg?w=959&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;crop=edges%2Centropy%2Cfaces&amp;trim=auto"/>
      <media:content url="https://publication.blendleimg.com/publication/newyorktimes/2019/07/02/item/34_1/version/1/image/original/1bce4ea30f8b96ce4ce89710f9d4095a78fdf43b.jpg?w=959&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;crop=edges%2Centropy%2Cfaces&amp;trim=auto">

      </media:content>
      <category>economy</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-08</pubDate>
      <description>That pilot episode, which aired
            60 years ago this fall and sold CBS on the cult series, dealt with the
            country’s early attempts to hurl humans into the cosmic void, depicting what viewers learn only late in
            the show is an astronaut trainee who has been in an isolation chamber for nearly three weeks. Many
            American TV watchers were still paranoid about the Sputnik launch two years earlier and didn’t know what
            lay ahead as man reached for the stars. For them, “Where Is Everybody?” (as the episode is titled) was a
            startling introduction to what the series creator, Rod Serling, called in his famous opening narration a
            realm “as vast as space and as timeless as infinity.”</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Minecraft Generation</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>economy</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-19</pubDate>
      <description>Presto: Jordan had used the cow’s weird behavior to create, in effect, a random-­number generator
            inside Minecraft. It was an ingenious bit of problem-­solving, something most computer engineers
            I know would regard as a great hack — a way of coaxing a computer system to do something new and
            clever.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Selfish Dataome - Nautilus</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>technology</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-09</pubDate>
      <description>You’ve heard the argument before: Genes are the permanent aristocracy of evolution, looking after themselves
            as fleshy hosts come and go. That’s the thesis of a book that, last year, was christened the most
            influential science book of all time: Richard Dawkins’ The Selfish Gene.

            But we humans actually generate far more actionable information than is encoded in all of our combined
            genetic material, and we carry much of it into the future. The data outside of our biological selves—call it
            the dataome—could actually represent the grander scaffolding for complex life. The dataome may provide a
            universally recognizable signature of the slippery characteristic we call intelligence, and it might even
            teach us a thing or two about ourselves.

            It is also something that has a considerable energetic burden. That burden challenges us to ask if we are
            manufacturing and protecting our dataome for our benefit alone, or, like the selfish gene, because the data
            makes us do this because that’s what ensures its propagation into the future.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Can You Die From a Broken Heart?</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>health</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-29</pubDate>
      <description>Ruth and Harold “Doc” Knapke met in elementary school. They exchanged letters during the war, when Doc was
            stationed in Germany. After he returned their romance began in earnest. They married, raised six children
            and celebrated 65 anniversaries together. And then on a single day in August 2013, in the room they shared
            in an Ohio nursing home, they died.

            “No relationship was ever perfect, but theirs was one of the better relationships I ever observed,” says
            their daughter Margaret Knapke, 61, a somatic therapist. “They were always like Velcro. They couldn’t stand
            to be separated.”</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>If Humble People Make the Best Leaders, Why Do We Fall for Charismatic Narcissists?</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://pocket-image-cache.com/direct?resize=w2000&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhbr.org%2Fresources%2Fimages%2Farticle_assets%2F2017%2F04%2Fapr17-07-610032338.jpg"/>
      <media:content url="https://pocket-image-cache.com/direct?resize=w2000&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhbr.org%2Fresources%2Fimages%2Farticle_assets%2F2017%2F04%2Fapr17-07-610032338.jpg">

      </media:content>
      <category>sports</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-23</pubDate>
      <description>The research is clear: when we
            choose humble, unassuming people as our leaders, the world around us becomes a better place.
            Humble leaders improve the performance of a company in the long run because they create more collaborative
            environments. They have a balanced view of themselves – both their virtues and shortcomings – and a strong
            appreciation of others’ strengths and contributions, while being open to new ideas and feedback. These
            “unsung heroes” help their believers to build their self-esteem, go beyond their expectations, and create a
            community that channels individual efforts into an organized group that works for the good of the
            collective.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Syytteistä vapautetut Kittilän kuntapäättäjät helpottuivat: ”Meistä on tehty roistoja jo alkuvaiheessa”</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/6</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/5d9bf8f0e2bd4b709677f271d67d3d21.jpg.webp"/>
      <media:content url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/5d9bf8f0e2bd4b709677f271d67d3d21.jpg.webp">

      </media:content>
      <category>technology</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-04</pubDate>
      <description>”Yleinen tunnelma on ollut huojentunut. Myös kuntalaiset ovat olleet positiivisella mielellä”, Kurula toteaa lyhyesti.Kurula toimi itsekin vuonna 2017 Kittilän virkaa tekevänä kunnanjohtajana. Kyseessä on ollut todellinen pätkäpesti, sillä Mäkelän erottamisen jälkeen määräaikaisia kunnanjohtajia on ollut jo neljä. Nyttemmin Kurula on palannut entiseen työhönsä Kittilän yläkoulun ja lukion biologian ja maantieteen opettajaksi.
Syytettyjen joukossa oli myös kunnanvaltuutettu Akseli Erkkilä</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Maratonoikeudenkäynti päättyi syyttäjien kannalta yllätykseen: kaikki Kittilän kuntapäättäjien syytteet hylättiin</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/7</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/ba1cca83c5b9436a8496dcf70b97232a.jpg.webp"/>
      <media:content url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/ba1cca83c5b9436a8496dcf70b97232a.jpg.webp">

      </media:content>
      <category>technology</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-08</pubDate>
      <description>Mäkelän oma toiminta kunnanjohtajana sen sijaan saa käräjäoikeudelta moitteita. Se ei ollut aina kunnan edun mukaista ja osoitti harkitsemattomuutta.Mäkelän potkuja valmistellut tilapäinen valiokunta pyrki hoitamaan tehtävänsä oikeuden mukaan ”erityisen huolellisesti”.”Todistelusta ei käynyt esille, että tilapäisen valiokunnan nimenomainen tarkoitus olisi ollut vahingon tai haitan aiheuttaminen Mäkelälle”, oikeus totesi ratkaisussaan.
Kihlakunnansyyttäjät Katri Junnikkala-Heikkinen</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Kolme suomalaiskeksintöä parantaa ihmisten elämää ympäri maailmaa, mutta harva tietää niiden alkuperää</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/8</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/f758d14e1e204921a01d4d1580e59cb2.jpg.webp"/>
      <media:content url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/f758d14e1e204921a01d4d1580e59cb2.jpg.webp">

      </media:content>
      <category>health</category>
      <pubDate>2019-06-10</pubDate>
      <description>Heikkilä on alun perin koulutuk­seltaan mikro­biologi, ja hän puolustaa kirjassaan tiedettä. Suuri osa innovaatioista pohjautuu tutkijoiden vuosien puurtamiseen aiheen parissa. Menestyneiden keksintöjen taustalla on usein pitkä ja kivinen tie.
Heikkilä nostaa nyt kolme merkittävää keksintöä kirjastaan.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Maailma tuottaa vuodessa 2,1 miljardia tonnia yhdyskuntajätettä, mutta USA on ylivoimainen ”jätekukkulan kuningas”</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:8000/hs/article/9</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/abc09803503b4e82902ab0de7ba37d51.jpg.webp"/>
      <media:content url="https://hs.mediadelivery.fi/img/1920/abc09803503b4e82902ab0de7ba37d51.jpg.webp">

      </media:content>
      <category>health</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-01</pubDate>
      <description>brittiläisen Verisk Maplecroft -yrityksen julkisten tietojen ja akateemisen tutkimuksen pohjalta luotuihin indekseihin. Toinen indeksi luotiin mittamaan kierrättämistä ja toinen jätteentuottamista.</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>