<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:iltalehti="https://www.iltalehti.fi/rss" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news</link>
    <description>None</description>
    <language>fi</language>
    <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 18:12:59 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Consider Before Trading Your Health Data for Cash</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://cdn.thewirecutter.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/00wc_datahealth_1024.png">

      </media:content>
      <category>politics</category>
      <pubDate>2019-06-09</pubDate>
      <description>If you work for a company with employer-sponsored health insurance, there’s a chance you’ve come across
            wellness programs such as UnitedHealthcare
                Motion, Humana Go365, Attain by Aetna, and Vitality (The New York Times, Wirecutter’s
            parent company, offers Vitality to its employees). Each program works similarly, offering some type of
            discount or financial incentive in exchange for reaching goals, usually verified by requesting health data
            collected by a phone or fitness tracker. Insurance companies offer these programs to encourage people to
            begin or maintain healthy habits, like eating well and exercising, thus reducing health care costs.
            Employers offer them as a way to provide financial rewards you can use toward the cost of insurance or gift
            cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to Gift Someone a Pet? Here’s What to Do First.</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://cdn.thewirecutter.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/00wc_petgift_1024.png">

      </media:content>
      <category>politics</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-20</pubDate>
      <description>Planting a big red bow on a new pet is endearing, but gifters should find alternatives to just showing up with a
            living being. I’m a fan of giving new pet owners a pet basket, like a new pet bed filled with treats,
            accessories, and a voucher for a complimentary visit to a veterinarian. As Wirecutter’s pets writer, I’ve
            written about what to buy before
                adopting a cat or dog,
            how to choose a pet food, and the importance
            of vaccinating and microchipping your pet.
            This not only eases some financial stress but also makes it feel less like a burden for recipients who aren&#39;t
            ready to welcome a new pet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Virtual Reality for a Test Drive</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://media.newyorker.com/photos/5dddb808996e66000803ba4c/master/w_727,c_limit/191209_r35551.jpg">

      </media:content>
      <category>economy</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-20</pubDate>
      <description>I pressed the Power button and found myself in the center of a computer-rendered 3-D glass geodesic dome
            with a million-dollar view of mountains. Sensors in the V.R. headset tracked my movements and
            instantaneously rejiggered the mise-en-scène. Gazing up, I saw stars; turning full circle, I took in a
            few Danish-modern sofas, a bookcase, and potted plants. Oh, look, I thought, my Oculus has a fireplace!
            (For a moment, I considered ditching my apartment and moving, with my headset, into a closet.) In the
            “living room” was an enormous floating display with a menu of options from Oculus—apps and games that I
            could buy for $9.99 to $29.99 (some are free). Should I travel aboard the International Space Station
            and experience zero gravity? Take a guided Tai Chi class? Create 3-D paintings in the air? Have a
            tête-à-tête with Jesus, who would lead me in a guided meditation? (The In His Presence V.R. Web
            site asks, “How can God fit into your crowded life with everything else on your plate?”) Disunion, the
            guillotine simulator, was discontinued, so I’d have to find another way to imagine what it was like to
            be executed during the French Revolution—perhaps I could download the app produced by Excedrin that
            allows one to feel what it’s like to have a migraine? (Philosophical query: Is it O.K. to cancel a
            real-life appointment because you have a virtual headache?)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech’s Big Defector</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://media.newyorker.com/photos/5dd70dcd76d5800008d6197c/master/w_727,c_limit/191202_r35501.jpg">

      </media:content>
      <category>health</category>
      <pubDate>2019-06-24</pubDate>
      <description>Among some skeptics, however, the profit McNamee has accrued from the technology that he now urges us
                    to renounce makes him difficult to trust. One view of McNamee is that he has the gravitas of a man
                    willing to admit that he was wrong. (“Shame on me,” he told one interviewer.) Another is that,
                    having successfully ridden one wave, he is trying to ride another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Have Been Practicing Social Responsibility For Decades, But Is That Really A Good Thing?</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://d.newsweek.com/en/full/1548831/fe-csr-01-1041330598-banner.webp">

      </media:content>
      <category>politics</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-18</pubDate>
      <description>Now, they have evolved even more. Many companies are now incorporating impact-on-society considerations
            into core business activities. For example, Starbucks only uses &#34;ethically-sourced coffee.&#34; Programs
            like these are often focused on &#34;sustainability.&#34; In August, 181 CEOs of the country&#39;s largest
            corporations signed a Business Roundtable statement committing to managing their companies not just for
            shareholders, but also for customers, employees, suppliers, and communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our nature crisis is also a human crisis.</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://miro.medium.com/max/1000/1*ySHR13eAgzYIVPvCrPBKcw.jpeg">

      </media:content>
      <category>technology</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-11</pubDate>
      <description>Tackling this ‘nature crisis’ may seem to many to be a remote,
            moral duty and not as pressing as other concerns, such as climate change. With many of us increasingly
            disconnected from nature, it is often perceived as a nice-to-have. Nothing could be further from the
            truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From College Grad to CEO: Three Seed-Stage Founders Share What It Takes to Start a Company</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/6</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="https://miro.medium.com/max/2000/1*t8nVu4aS98AKHnJpj9WI_Q.png">

      </media:content>
      <category>sports</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-22</pubDate>
      <description>We chose to work with Sequoia in particular because we get to work
            with Alfred Lin, and he was able to bring his experience and point of view, which made a lot of sense
            for us. Our crypto investor is super involved in crypto and into the ethos of the space, whereas Alfred
            is more about being pragmatic and growing the business. That mix of perspectives is really helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Finance - AVC</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/7</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>sports</category>
      <pubDate>2019-05-17</pubDate>
      <description>While we wait for the blockchain/crypto technology to scale to the point where it can be the foundation
            of mainstream consumer applications (games, social media, e-commerce, etc), there is a sector where
            scalability is a little less important and where blockchain/crypto is starting to show some real signs
            of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypothetical Value To Real Value</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/8</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>sports</category>
      <pubDate>2019-06-15</pubDate>
      <description>A few weeks later he asked me “Dad, what is a PE ratio?” So I said to him “you know that deli that you
            stop in every morning and get a bacon egg and cheese on the way to school?” He said “yes”. I said “let’s
            say tomorrow the owner says to you, I’m selling the business, do you want to buy it? We make $1mm a year
            in profits and have for the last thirty years.” Then I said, “how much would you pay him for it?” My son
            thought about it and said “Four to five million dollars.” I asked him why. He said, “Because I would get
            my money back in four to five years and then make a million dollars a year after that.” I said, “you
            offered to pay a PE of 4 to 5.” And he said, “Oh, I get it.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AirPods Pro First Impressions</title>
      <link>http://tridample.eu.pythonanywhere.com/news/article/9</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9</guid>
      <enclosure url=""/>
      <media:content url="">

      </media:content>
      <category>politics</category>
      <pubDate>2019-07-07</pubDate>
      <description>I was a dummy and didn’t take my Bose headphones on my trip today, so I can’t say how they compare
            side-by-side on the train, but there’s no question how AirPods Pro compare to regular AirPods. The
            difference is like night and day. Amtrak trains are pretty noisy — especially at what we in the U.S. so
            adorably consider “high speeds” — but with AirPods Pro the clackety-clack rumble was effectively blocked
            out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>